http://www.salamanderdesigns.com/privacy-policy/

Home
/
Privacy Policy
15% Off
Select Lancaster Cabinets For A Limited Time!
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the salamanderdesigns.com and Salamander Designs Ltd. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Salamander Designs Ltd. include salamanderdesigns.com and Salamander. The Salamander website is a Company and Product Information and ecommerce site. By using the Salamander website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Salamander may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Salamander's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. Salamander may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income and Personal interests. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Salamander. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Salamander website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Salamander's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.
Salamander encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Salamander so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Salamander is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Salamander website.
Use of your Personal Information
Salamander collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
Salamander may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Salamander and its affiliates. Salamander may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Salamander does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Salamander may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Salamander may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Salamander, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Salamander may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Salamander, in order to determine what Salamander services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Salamander to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Salamander will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Salamander or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Salamander; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Salamander, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Salamander website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Salamander pages, or register with Salamander site or services, a cookie helps Salamander to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Salamander website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Salamander features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Salamander services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Salamander secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Children Under Thirteen
Salamander does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Salamander by contacting us here:
Web page: salamanderdesigns.com
Email: webmaster@salamanderdesigns.com
Phone: 860-761-9500
Changes to this Statement
Salamander will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Salamander encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Salamander is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Salamander welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Salamander has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Salamander at:
Salamander Designs Ltd.
811 Blue Hills Avenue
Bloomfield, Connecticut 06002
Email Address:
info@salamanderdesigns.com
Telephone number:
860-761-9500
Effective as of January 1, 2013
